<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE book PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.4//EN"
"http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.4/docbookx.dtd" [
<!ENTITY % xinclude SYSTEM "../../../../target/doc-base/dtd/xinclude.mod">
%xinclude;
]>

<chapter>
	<title>Introduction</title>
	
	<section>
		<title>Overview</title>
		<para>
			The UCIPLink is a standalone system integrating the charging system and the txe.
		</para>
	</section>

	<section>
		<title>Mappings of service class values to account link type id</title>
		<para>
			The uciplink supports mapping of service class ranges to groups that are used by the TXE business logic rules.
			These mappings are enabled and configured in the uciplink.properties files and is returned back to TXE in the
			getAccountInformation response accountLinkTypeId field.
		</para>
	</section>

	<section>
		<title>Mapping of account status</title>
		<para>
			The uciplink supports mapping of account status returned back to the client in the getAccountInformationResponse. This mapped
			status is used by the TXE business rule to allow/disallow R2S and P2P requests.
		</para>
		<para>
			The mapping uses the supervisionExpirtyDate and the serviceFeeExpirtyDate from the charging system. The supervisionExpriyDate
			is the grace period when you can receive sms and calls whiel the serviceFeeExpiryDate is the date where the account is totally de-activated.
		</para>
		<para>
			The account status is set according to the following:
		</para><para>	
A=supervisionExpiryDate=grace period when you can receive sms and calls
		</para><para>	
B=serviceFeeExpiryDate=the account is totally de-activated
		</para><para>	

1. Check if the account has been activated (and thus has been assigned an end
date for service fee.
		</para><para>	

A=not set => AccountStatus.Pending (The account is pending, ie it might be a
new account that has not been activate yet etc)
		</para><para>	


2. Check if the account is totally de-activated.
		</para><para>	

current time > A => AccountStatus.Disabled
		</para><para>	

3. Check if the account is in grace period where the user can receive SMS and
calls or is not set yet.
		</para><para>	

current time > B or B is not set => AccountStatus.Suspended (The account has
been suspended, and has limited services allowed)
		
		</para>
	</section>

</chapter>
