<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE book PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.4//EN"
"http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.4/docbookx.dtd" [
<!ENTITY % xinclude SYSTEM "../../../../target/doc-base/dtd/xinclude.mod">
%xinclude;
]>

<chapter>
	<title>Developer section</title>

	<para>
		This chapter contains the technical details for this link component intended 
		to be used by those who use this link for integration to the charging system.
		Note that this link can communicate with the CS3Simulator and Charging system
		only using the UCIP protocol.
	</para>
	<para>
		This chapter is organized in sections and each section describes the necessary
		details of service functions.
	</para>
	<section>
		<title>Service getAccountInformation</title>
		<para>
			This service fetches the account information from the charging system if the
			account exists in the charging system. The basic parameters it requires are
			listed in the following table. 
		</para>
		<para>
		<table border="1" >
			<title>Basic parameters for getAccountInformation service</title>
			<thead>
				<tr>
				<th>Parameter</th>
				<th>Description</th>
				</tr>
			</thead>
			<tbody>
				<tr>
				<td>principalId</td>
				<td>The id of the subsystem consuming this service, such as ERS</td>
				</tr>
				<tr>
				<td>account</td>
				<td>The account type and id of the subscriber whose information is required to be fetched</td>
				</tr>
				<tr>
				<td>routingInfo</td>
				<td>Any routing instruction for the particular account</td>
				</tr>
				<tr>
				<td>wantBalance</td>
				<td>If the balance information is required along with the account information</td>
				</tr>
				<tr>
				<td>reference</td>
				<td>A reference id for charging system for this transaction</td>
				</tr>
			</tbody>
		</table>
		</para>
		
		<para>
			Upon the successful completion of the transaction, the following information is returned back to the service consumer.
		</para>
		<para>
		<table border="1" >
			<title>Response information for getAccountInformation service</title>
			<thead>
				<tr>
				<th>Parameter</th>
				<th>Description</th>
				</tr>
			</thead>
			<tbody>
				<tr>
				<td>prepared</td>
				<td>Whether the operation was a prepare for a commit and if the operation is now prepared</td>
				</tr>
				<tr>
				<td>accountData</td>
				<td>As per documented in the AccountData class. Information related to the fields is described below</td>
				</tr>
				<tr>
				<td>accountData.fields.serviceOffering_?</td>
				<td>If there are service offerings enable for the account they will be present in the fields table. The key
				is in the format of for example "serviceOffering_?" where '?' can be any digit from 0 to 31. The value is 
				always "true" since the service offerings with a value "false" are not returned.</td>
				</tr>
				<tr>
				<td>accountData.fields.activationStatusFlag</td>
				<td>One of the flag from the account flags in the charging system. The value can be "true" or "false"</td>
				</tr>				
			</tbody>
		</table>
		</para>
		
	</section>	
	
</chapter>
